{
    "id": "4afb1027355340b8a6e4a0977c32ebf5",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .................................. the bell six times but no one opened the door.",
            "description": "The past tense of ring is rang.",
            "answers": [
                "rang",
                "ringed",
                "rung"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ce2a6bb148a4b8b983793365ffec2ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you .................................. your violin?",
            "description": "The past and past participle form of bring is brought.",
            "answers": [
                "bringed",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8141f7d140c64866a1daf75f1bbf5319"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat has ................................ all the milk.",
            "description": "We need a past participle form after has, have and had. The past participle of drink is drunk.",
            "answers": [
                "drunk",
                "drinked",
                "drank"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eb3cde5c6ef1444ab658ad759166185c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ...................................... your duty?",
            "description": "The past participle of do is done. ",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2cb9ab16a79e49b9bc9521a7ebdc30bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ..................................... a deep well in the yard.",
            "description": "The past and past participle of dig is dug.",
            "answers": [
                "digged",
                "dug",
                "dugged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "997d4c425ce44c4faa4a626237041f8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You needn't have .................................... that much money on that coat.",
            "description": "The past participle of spend is spent.",
            "answers": [
                "spend",
                "spent",
                "spended"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a448dcf661ca4b27ac526c5d134b7502"
        },
        {
            "question": "That shirt ................................. me 80 dollars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cost",
                "costed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "679aa34eccfd4fbb85b187abe32294ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldiers ..................................... that they would never surrender.",
            "description": "Swore is the past participle of swear.",
            "answers": [
                "swore",
                "sworn",
                "sweared"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da4bffb2a09845afa1c8951c24b30a5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I got ...................................... in the traffic jam for two hours.",
            "description": "Stuck is the past participle of stick. ",
            "answers": [
                "sticked",
                "stuck",
                "stucked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fba9e6db1a3e4a90879f4d4efcd81301"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ......................................... fifty miles.",
            "description": "Strode is the past tense of stride.",
            "answers": [
                "strided",
                "strode",
                "stroded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18f4985b602c488ba7ba3f0a5fb8bc28"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ........................................ up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "grew",
                "grown",
                "growed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a223d0eb0533494e95a7c71c33be3469"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................... unconsciousness on the pavement.",
            "description": "Lay is the past tense of lie.",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "lay",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e3f7cc9ce644ef79971f65dbcd80f21"
        }
    ]
}